CLYDE PABRO

Seeking Entry Level Full Stack Web Developer Position

4239 Middlebury Way Mather, CA 95655 (916) 849-2062 clydepabro@gmail.com www.madnoyz.com

SUMMARY

A student in Full Stack Web Development with experience and extensive education in software design and web development. A fast learner with strong time management and multitasking skills. Effective work ethic in a team or individual setting to drive product success and process efficiency. Strong troubleshooting and problem solving skills with an analytical and curious mindset.

EMPLOYMENT

City of West Sacramento, West Sacramento, CA Application Developer Intern

SEP 2016 - JUNE 2017

Developed a mobile application for Mayor Christopher L. Cabaldon for use within the community. SCRUM software development methodology and modern web technologies were utilized in the creation of this app.

City of West Sacramento, West Sacramento, CA *Graphic Production Artist*

OCT 2013 - SEP 2016

Managed the development of creative solutions through visual communication. Lead the graphic design and implementation of corporate advertising campaigns and concepts for print/web media. Also, photographed various media events.

Murphy's Magic Supplies, Inc., Rancho Cordova, CA *Graphic Production Artist*

NOV 2008 - SEP 2011

Designed and developed graphics for website, user interfaces, and advertising. Implemented a dvd-to-web conversion protocol for use with their online streaming business.

EDUCATION

Sacramento State University, Sacramento, CA Bachelor's of Science Computer Science

SEP 2014 - MAY 2017

Folsom Lake College, Folsom, CA Associate's Degree in Computer Science and Mathematics

MAY 2008 - MAY 2014

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: C, C++, Java, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Angular, Node, SQL, PHP, Python, VB.net

Database: Postgres SQL, MySQL, MS Access.

Cloud: AWS Amazon Web Services, Heroku, Firebase

Applications: Adobe Creative Suite, MS Office – Word, Excel, Outlook, Windows, Linux, OSX, Visual Studio Code, Sublime Text, Vim, Eclipse, Github, Git

OTHER SKILLS

Github.com/madnoyz

Linkedin.com/in/clydepabro

Built a self-driving car with Texas Instrument microcontroller and remote controlled car.

Previously owned a Airsoft/Paintball retail store.

Participated in Intel Ultimate Engineer Experience - hackathon, robotics programming, startup entrepreneurship.